New England Archivists, Inc. Records 1992.0012
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series V: Subject Files, undated, 1977-
  - Retreat, 1986 (Box 18:915)
  - Regionals, 1979-1981 (Box 18:916)
  - State Archivist Survey, 1996 (Box 18:917)
  - Webpages, undated (Box 18:918-921)
  - Whitaker Chronological File, 1977-1981 (Box 18:922)
  - Whitaker Chronological File, 1982-1983 (Box 18:923)
- Series VI: Special Formats, 1973-1993
  - 3 reels of single track audio tape (Box 19)
    - Session on oral history, 1973
    - New England Document Conservation Center, 1973
    - Lee Speech (side l); Business meeting (side 2), 1973
  - 10 audio cassettes (Box 19)
    - Joyce Bassett, photo duplication session, undated
    - Business meeting (2 cassettes), undated
    - Collecting papers, undated
    - NEA Meeting (3 cassettes), 1974 November 9
    - George Vogt, Historical Documentary publication, undated
    - Alternatives to Book publishing, 1981
    - Promoting your collections, undated
  - Business cards, undated (Box 19)
  - Photographs (Box 19)
    - Archives week, undated
    - Big E, 1990
    - Gregory Sanford, 1990
    - Meeting--Fall, 1998
    - Transparency: image for folders, undated
  - Proclamation: New England Archivists Week in CT, 1988-1989 (Box 20)
  - Proclamation: New Hampshire Archives Week, 1989 (Box 20)
  - Proclamation: Connecticut Archives Week, 2006 (Box 20)
  - Proclamation: Massachusetts Archives Week, 2002, 2004-2005, 2007 (Box OS)
  - Proclamation: Maine Archives Week, 2004 (Box 20)
  - Banner (red), undated (Box 20)
  - Exhibition Photographs: NEA Achivists in Their Natural Habitats (Box 20), 1993 (Box 20)